expresspros.com 2011-12-31

# Privacy Policy | Express Employment Professionals

### Protecting Your Privacy

We respect the privacy rights our clients, employees, applicants, associates and those we conduct business with. Any information provided to Express, or that is gathered by Express, will be kept strictly confidential and will only be used or shared in ways for which you have specifically consented. Unless we have your express consent, Express will not sell, rent, loan, trade or lease your personal information to any third party. We will use the utmost care in protecting the privacy and security of your information. This policy explains our information practices the ways Express collects and uses information. This Privacy Policy covers the information you provide to us offline and at Express’ web sites. Our Privacy Policy does not apply to third party web sites that may be accessible through Express web sites. We encourage you to read the privacy policies of those third parties to learn how they collect and use information about you.

####  Collection And Use Of Information

Express collects and uses personal information to respond to requests for information, products and services. Unless we have your express consent, your personal information will only be used or shared to fulfill your request. Express collects personal information when you: 

  * Subscribe to newsletters or utilize our web sites to seek employment or employees. Your e-mail address is collected and will only be used to send you the newsletter(s) or the services you have requested. You may subscribe or unsubscribe from our e-mail communications at any time.
  * Request for Express' staffing services. Information such as name, e-mail address, phone number, physical address and company-related information may be requested. If you purchase one of our services, we may also collect a valid credit card number, expiration date and billing address.
  * Participate in a promotion or online survey in which we ask you for contact information (like e-mail address), and we may ask for additional optional survey information (like service preferences). We use this information to administer the program or activity, to notify winners, and, if you give us your opt-in consent at the time we collect your information, to send you promotional materials.
  * Contact Express with a question or suggestion in which we collect your name, e-mail address and any comments you have. We only use this information to respond to and/or resolve your question or concern.
  * Apply for employment with Express. We ask you to submit your contact information and resume. This information will only be used to evaluate your qualifications for the desired position and possibly to contact you for further information. Resume Viewing: If you choose to place a resume with us, your information will be available to all our franchise offices and our two professional placement affiliates (RWJ and Express Professional). Your information will not be made available to outside companies or entities.
  * When accessing Express Web sites, we may give you the option of submitting other general information, such as company name, title and how you heard about Express. Optional information is requested to help us better understand our clients, customers and Web visitors. If you have requested that we send you additional information regarding Express service and events, we may also use the optional information to fulfill this request.
  * Technical information When you visit our Web site, Express may collect technical information that does not by itself identify a specific individual. This information (sometimes referred to as "non- personally identifiable information") may include the address (or "URL") of the Web site that you came from before visiting our site, which pages you visit on our site, which browser you used to view our site and any search terms you have entered on our site. This technical data is aggregated and used to measure and improve the effectiveness of the Express Web site. We do not attempt to combine this technical data with the personal information we collect on our site.

####  Cookies, Web Beacons And Third Party Advertisers

Cookies may be used to keep track of what you have selected as you click through our site. When filling out an online forms, session cookies may be used to capture an applicant's progress as they complete portions of the forms up to and including the point of submission. We may use cookies to allow you to access areas of our Web site that are limited to registered users. We do not, however, use cookies to track the navigational habits of identified visitors. Furthermore, we do not allow other companies (third parties) to set cookies via Express Web sites. Most browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually refuse cookies, or selectively accept cookies, by adjusting the preferences in your browser. If you turn cookies off, there may be some features of our site that will not be available to you and some Web pages may not display properly. You can find information about how you can adjust your cookie setting at the following Web sites: Microsoft Internet Explorer: <http://www.microsoft.com/info/cookies.htm> and Netscape Navigator: [ http://www.netscape.com/legal_notices/cookies.html](http://www.netscape.com/legal_notices/cookies.html). Express web sites do not use electronic images known as Web beacons, or clear GIFs to monitor the activity of our Web site. Express does not use third party advertising companies to provide advertisements or allow third party advertisers to track your browsing activities on Express web sites.

####  Sharing Information

Unless we have your express consent, Express will not sell, rent, loan, trade or lease personal information such as membership data or e-mail lists to any third party. We treat all information you provide as confidential. Occasionally, we may contract with other companies to provide limited services on our behalf such as packaging, mailing and delivering orders and processing event registration. From time to time, we may be required to provide personal information in response to a valid court order, subpoena, government investigation, or as otherwise required by law. Unless prevented by law, we will notify you prior to the release of such information. We also reserve the right to report to law enforcement agencies any activities that we, in good faith, believe to be unlawful. We may release certain personal information when we believe that such release is reasonably necessary to protect the rights, property, and safety of others and ourselves.

####  How Information Is Used

You remain in control of your information. Express will not use or share the personal information we collect in ways unrelated to the purpose for which you provided the information without first obtaining your consent (opt-in). At the time you provide your information, you can choose whether you want to receive further communications about special offers, product information or other marketing messages. If we collect your information and you are not presented with a choice, that indicates the information you submit will only be used to fulfill your request. If you do opt-in to marketing communications from Express, you can opt-out at any time. All e-mail communications from us, such as newsletters, tell you how to stop receiving them.

####  Security Of Personal Information

Express uses a variety of safeguards to protect your information from loss, misuse, alteration or destruction. For example, we use internet and network security technology to prevent unauthorized parties from viewing any personal information transmitted to or from Express. We only provide access to your personal information to Express employees and other authorized parties on a "need to know" basis. We have also registered with Verisign and have obtained digital certificates for our web sites and subdomains, allowing your browser to confirm our server's identity. Please be careful whenever sending personal information to Express via e-mail. E-mail commonly may not be a completely secure means of transferring information.

####  How Long Information Is Stored

Express believes it is important, for privacy and security reasons, to delete information when it is no longer needed. Data retention periods differ depending on the type of information collected and its intended purpose. For example, we will store your e- mail address if you've subscribed to one of our newsletters until you opt-out (tell us you no longer wish to receive communications from us). If you order services from us, account and billing information will be archived according to legal requirements. If you send us a question or concern, we will maintain your information for a reasonable period of time and then delete it.

####  Privacy Policy Changes

If there are changes or additions to this Privacy Policy, we will post those changes so that you will always know what information we collect online or offline, how we use it and what choices you have. Regardless of any changes we make to our Privacy Policy, we will only use your personal information in accordance with the version of the Privacy Policy in place at the time you provided your information, unless you later give your express consent for us to do otherwise.

####  Contact Us

If you wish to change or delete your registration information or opt-out of any promotional materials please contact Express Employment Professionals International Headquarters in the manner described below.

If you have any questions or complaints regarding our personal information handling practices and policies, please contact our Express Employment Professionals International Headquarters.

Express Services Inc.  
8516 NW Expressway  
Oklahoma City, OK 73162  
Phone: 1-405-840-5000  
Fax: 1-405-717-5516  
Email the Webmaster

We will address your concern and attempt to resolve any problem.
